Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee College of Health Sciences Records, 1960-2013
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
UW-Milwaukee College of Health Sciences Records, 1960-2013
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. College of Health Sciences. Office of the Dean
UWM Archival Collection 49
Accession 1998-048
Accession 2001-014
Accession 2002-075
Accession 2003-047
Accession 2007-016
Accession 2010-003
Accession 2016-010
34 cubic ft. (40 boxes) 104 digital files (187 MB) plus additions of 12 cubic ft. (16 boxes)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Records created or collected by the dean of the College of Health Sciences (formerly the School of Allied Health Professions), containing brochures and bulletins; correspondence; faculty meeting minutes; various committee files, including miscellaneous search and screen committee records; and teaching evaluation summaries. The records largely document course and curriculum development, including the development of a bachelor of science in allied health and several master's and PhD programs; staffing, budget, and space needs; and committee activities. Information about the departments within the school can also be found in the collection, particularly in the correspondence, minutes, and curriculum files. The collection also contains unclassified personnel records which are restricted.
The School of Allied Health Professions was established in August 1975. In 2001, the name of the school was changed to the College of Health Sciences.
Deans of the School
1975-1976 Roslyn P. Warren (Acting)
1976-1981 Alan J. Weston
1981-1982 Ward K. Gates (Acting)
1982-1983 Erika Sander (Acting)
1983-1998 Frederick W. Pairent
1998-2008 Randall Lambrecht
2008-2009 Johannes Britz (Interim)
2009-2014 Chukuka S. Enwemeka
2014-2015 Paula M. Rhyner (Interim)
2015- Ron Cisler (Interim)
Materials from the various offices and departments of the College of Health Sciences. The majority of the collection consists of departmental meeting minutes and subject files from the constituent departments of the College of Health Sciences: the Dept. of Clinical Laboratory Sciences; the Dept. of Communication Sciences and Disorders; the Dept. of Health Sciences; the Dept. of Human Kinetics, including the Kinesiology program; the Dept. of Speech Pathology and Audiology; the Health Information Administration Program (later renamed the Department of Healthcare Administration and Informatics); the Health Career Opportunity Program; the J. Martin Klotsche Center for Physical Education; the Medical Technology Program; and the Dept. of Occupational Therapy. Most of the files within these departments deal with the addition of new courses or degree programs. Also included are numerous files related to the accreditation process for programs, departments, and the entire college.
The general files of the School include materials on special projects and relationships maintained by the Dean's Office, including Allied Health Week, affiliation agreements with public health institutions in Milwaukee, information on remodeling of Enderis and Lapham halls, and files on the School's participation in the Milwaukee Initiative and Milwaukee Idea. Of particular interest are files on the establishment of a collaborative physical therapy program with UW-La Crosse, as well as a large number of files on the budget and program priorities of the College. The College of Health Sciences was responsible for much of the planning of UWM's School of Public Health, and planning for that new campus unit is reflected in the collection. Also included are yearly planning documents, UWM internal reviews of the College as a whole, grant information, and information on credit and curriculum changes.
Box 7 was noted as missing on February 20, 2009. An inventory of the folders in this box is available in the collection case file. Ask an archivist for more information.
This collection was received in, and is organized in, multiple parts. Additional materials have not been physically or intellectually arranged and interfiled, and researchers may need to consult more than one part of the collection to locate similar materials.
UWM Archival Collection 49: Records, 1971-2013
The collection contains seven additional accessions.
Accession 1998-048: Personnel Files and Grants, 1977-1994
Accession 2001-014: Administrative Records and Personnel Files, 1963-2000
Accession 2002-075: Personnel Files, 1978-2002
Accession 2003-047: Personnel Files, 1992-1997
Accession 2007-016: Personnel Files, 1963-2002
Accession 2010-003: Personnel Files, 1972-2004
Accession 2016-010: Personnel Files, 1979-2013
An inventory of the personnel files in boxes 3-11, 16, and 34 is available in the Archives' case files. Finding aids for accessions 1998-048, 2001-014, 2002-075, 2003-047, 2007-016, 2010-003, and 2016-010 are also available in the Archives.
A file-level inventory of the electronic images in the collection is available in the archives. This inventory includes information about the date of creation, the file size and image dimensions, file formats, and embedded keywords provided by UWM Photo Services. See an archivist for more information.
Related Material in the UWM Libraries
J. Martin Klotsche Center for Physical Education (Milwaukee, Wis.) Publications UWM Archival Collection 36
UW-Milwaukee Dept. of Health Sciences Records UWM Archival Collection 61
UW-Milwaukee Dept. of Human Kinetics Records UWM Archival Collection 53
UW-Milwaukee Dept. of Speech Pathology and Audiology Records UWM Archival Collection 57
UW-Milwaukee Medical Record Administration Program Records UWM Archival Collection 54
UW-Milwaukee Medical Technology Program Records UWM Archival Collection 55
UW-Milwaukee Occupational Therapy Program Records UWM Archival Collection 60
Administrative/Restriction Information
As of November 1, 2016, all electronic files were accessible on an Intel Core i5-4570 CPU (3.20 GHz, 4 GB RAM) running Windows 7 Enterprise with service pack 1. Windows Picture and Fax Viewer, Microsoft Office 2016, and LibreOffice were used to access the files.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
JPEG File Interchange Format[.jpg]
Microsoft Word Document 6.0 [.doc]
Microsoft Word Document 97-2003 [.doc]
Acrobat PDF - Portable Document Format [.pdf]
The unclassified personnel files in boxes 3-11, 16, and 35 as well as accessions 1998-048 (box 2), 2002-075, 2003-047, 2007-016, 2010-003, 2016-010, and boxes 3-4 of 2001-014 are restricted in accordance with UWM Personnel File Policy S-42. Access is regulated by Section III.A.2 and III.A.3. Additional folders in box 19 are restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act on 1973 (FERPA).
There are no access restrictions on the rest of the collection, which is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
An unknown individual transferred the collection to the Archives prior to 1989. Kristene Lindert transferred materials in January 1998 (accession 1998-048). Patti Sander donated additional material in October 2001 (accession 2001-014). The College of Health Sciences transferred accessions 2011-049 and 2012-005 to the Archives in June-July 2012. The College of Health Sciences transferred electronic photos (accession 2013-002) in July 2013 and additional records (accession 2016-010) in August 2016.
Contents List
- Records, 1960-2013, UWM Archival Collection 49; 34 cubic ft. (40 boxes) 104 digital files (187 MB)
  - Academic Affairs Budget, 1982-1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Planning, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Academic Planning Committee, 1989-1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Tenure Criteria, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Affiliation Agreements, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allied Health Week, 1988-1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Survey, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - American Occupational Therapy Foundation Grant, 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report and Sketch Plan, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Association of Schools of Allied Health Professions
    - 1987-1988, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
    - Annual Conferences, 1986-2007 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Archives, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Audiology Doctorate, Planning and Proposal, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Awards and Plaques
    - 1974-2004 (Box 36)
    - 1984-1994 (Box 37)
  - Bachelor of Science in Allied Health
    - Audit and Review, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - New Academic Program Request, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7 8)
    - Proposal to Implement, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bachelor of Science in Therapeutic Recreation, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Brochures, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Budget Planning Documents
    - 1982-1983, undated (Box 12, Folder 11-13)
    - 1983-1991 (Box 17, Folder 9-17)
    - 1988-2000 (Box 18, Folder 1-17)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
  - Bulletins, 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Center for Rehabilitation: Research and Education, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Centers, UWM Review, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Clinical Laboratory Sciences
    - 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
    - Academic Planning and Curriculum Committee Audit and Review, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Accreditation, 1974-1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Bachelor of Science Audit and Review
      - 1976 (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
      - Follow-up to 1975-1976 Review, 1976-1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Health Science Advisory Council, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - UWM Internal Program Evaluation, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, General, 1994-1999 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Cytotechnology
      - Accreditation, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Self Study
        - 1999 (Box 19, Folder 9)
        - 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10-11)
        - 2008 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1988-1995 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Forensic Science
      - 2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Brochure, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Program Review, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Master of Science Program Development, 1973, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 24-25)
    - Medical Technology Program
      - BS Audit and Review, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 16-17)
      - Consortium Arrangement, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Form C, Implement a Master of Science Degree, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Information and Self Evaluation Report, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 20-21)
      - Proposal for Master of Science in Medical Technology, 1978-1983 (Box 19, Folder 23-25)
    - Molecular Diagnostics Certificate, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - M.S. Program
      - 1994-1998 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Audit and Review, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - National Accrediting Agency for Clinical Laboratory Sciences Accreditation, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Planning Document, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Program Review, 1992-2005 (Box 20, Folder 2-5)
  - College of Health Deans, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Communication Sciences and Disorders
    - Academic Planning and Curriculum Committee/Graduate Faculty Council Review, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 7-9)
    - Accreditation
      - 1970-2003 (Box 20, Folder 10-13)
      - 1972-1991 (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
    - Annual Report, 1989-1994 (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
    - Center for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Dept. of Public Instruction, 1980-1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1990-1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Review, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Hearing Evaluation Center, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Master of Science Program Review, 1972-1978 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
    - Name Change, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Planning Document, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Program Development, 1964-1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Program Review, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 19-21)
    - Speech Clinic, 1975-1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Speech Pathology and Audiology
      - Accreditation, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Accreditation, 1980-1997 (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
      - Department Meeting Minutes, 1988-1995 (Box 13, Folder 31-32)
      - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Graduate Faculty Council Document #550, MS, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Program Review, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence
    - 1971-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13-17)
    - 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - 1982-1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1996-1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Course and Curriculum Committee
    - 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1982-1995 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Credit Analysis Report Summaries, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Curriculum Analysis, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dept. of Health Sciences
    - Bachelor of Science in Allied Health Program, Faculty Meetings, 1987-1995 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Bachelor of Science in Health Sciences, 1977-1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Department Meeting Minutes, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - DHHS/PHS/National Institute of Health Grant, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - EMS Building, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Enderis Hall Remodeling, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Documents, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Research Directory, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Faculty-Student Affairs Committee
    - 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Fifth International Conference on Healthcare Systems
    - 2008 (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
    - Proceedings, 2008
  - Forensic Science Certificate, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Faculty Council Documents, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Health Career Opportunity Program
    - Application, 1987, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Reapplication, 1983, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Health Information Administration
    - Accreditation, 1978-1993 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Directory, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - American Medical Record Administration, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Audit and Review, 1983-1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Bachelor of Science Program Proposal, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Honors Program, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1988-1995 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Healthcare Administration and Informatics
    - Academic Planning Committee, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Academic Program, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Accreditation, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - New Program Authorization, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 18-20)
    - Undergraduate Self-Study, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Undergraduate Self-Study, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - History of the School of Allied Health Professions Planning, 1984-1999 (Box 22, Folder 2-4)
  - Human Kinetics
    - 1985 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Adult Fitness Program, 1982-1984, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1989 (Box 39, Folder 1-4)
    - Department Meeting Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1979, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 21-22)
    - Faculty/Staff Meeting Minutes, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Graduate Faculty Committee Meeting Minutes, 1988-1992 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Kinesiology
      - Academic Program and Curriculum Committee Audit and Review, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
      - Graduate Program Review, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
      - Undergraduate Program Review, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Master of Science in Human Kinetics
      - 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Five-Year Joint UWM/UWS Review, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Follow-up Report to 1987-1988 Review, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Planning for Degree, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Proposal, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Planning Document, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Recreation Program, 1982-1992 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Report, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Science and Engineering Comparison of Actual Expenses, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Second 5-year Review, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Transfer Materials
      - Department of Physical Education, Recreation and Health Education, 1977-1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - School of Allied Health Professions, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - School of Education, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Transfer Negotiations
      - General, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Petition Papers, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - IBM Corporation Grant, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Interdisciplinary Preservice Preparation for Personnel Serving Preschool/Primary Children and Families in Culturally and Linguistically Diverse Urban Settings, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Investment
    - Assessment Steering Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
    - Proposals, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Proposals, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - UWM Process, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - J. Martin Klotsche Center for Physical Education
    - Annual Reports, 1980-1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Audit, 1980-1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Building Addition, 1984-1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1988 (Box 40, Folder 3-6)
    - Policies and Procedures, History Agreement for Use, 1989, undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Kohler Company Grant, 1995-1998 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Lapham Hall Remodeling, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Lateral Audits, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 4-12)
  - Lexiculization Processes in Stuttering Children Grant, 1997-1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Master of Science in Medical Technology
    - 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Follow-up Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Medical Center of Southeastern Wisconsin, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Medical College of Wisconsin, Cooperative Research Projects, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Medical Records Administration
    - Audit Report on BS Program, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - BS Degree Proposal, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Self-Evaluation of Educational Program, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 15-18)
    - Self-Study, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 19-21)
    - Self-Study, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 1-9)
  - Medical Technology Program, Minutes, 1972-1978 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Meeting Minutes
    - Administrative Staff
      - 1977-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
      - 1987-1995 (Box 12, Folder 2-5)
    - Committees, 2001-2008 (Box 24, Folder 10-17)
    - Committees, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - Course and Curriculum Committee, 1980-1996 (Box 25, Folder 3-8)
    - Dean's Administrative Staff Meeting, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Dean's Cabinet Meeting Documents
      - 2000-2007 (Box 25, Folder 10-15)
      - 2006-2008 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Department Minutes and Program Information
      - 2000-2007 (Box 26, Folder 2-8)
      - 2007-2010 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
    - Faculty/Academic Staff Meeting Minutes
      - 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - 2000-2008 (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes
      - 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
      - 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - Milwaukee Idea
    - 1999-2001 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Allocation Process, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Consortium for Economic Opportunity, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Documents, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 9-11)
    - Initiatives and Action Plans, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Matching Fund Allocations, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Second Ideas, 2000-2002 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Milwaukee Initiative II Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Milwaukee Regional Cancer Care Network, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - National Evaluation and Health Data System, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - New Academic Program Request
    - 1978 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - BS Health Sciences, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - New Program Authorization, PhD, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 17-18)
  - Occupational Therapy
    - Accreditation Materials
      - Accreditation Council for Occupational Therapy Education Self-Study, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
      - Accreditation Document, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
      - Application for Accreditation, 1975-1982 (Box 28, Folder 6-11)
      - American Occupational Therapy Association Accreditation, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Approvals, 1974-1989 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Biennial Report, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Continuing Accreditation Self-Study Document, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 15-17)
      - Reports and Essentials, 1975-1993 (Box 14, Folder 27-28)
    - American Occupational Therapy Association, 1973-1993 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Audit and Review
      - 1983-1989 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - 1988 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Bachelor of Science Program Development, 1972-1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum, 1986, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
    - Department Status, 1982, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Development, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
    - Graduate Program Report, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Program Review, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
    - Master of Science Program Development, 1988-1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - MS New Program Authorization, 1991-1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - MS Proposal, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Program Reviews (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - 2004 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - BS Review, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - MS Degree Joint Review, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Proposal for BS, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Proposal for Departmental Status, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Student Issues, 1988-2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Restricted
  - Older Adult Fitness Certificate, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - One-Time Funding Proposals, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 15-16)
  - Physical Therapy
    - 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Accreditation Standards, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Physical Therapy Program, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Approvals, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 20-21)
    - Audit, UW-System, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Budget and Audit Documents, 1998-2006 (Box 29, Folder 23-24)
    - Curriculum, 1994-1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Doctorate Program, UW-La Crosse
      - 1994-2004 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Memorandum of Understanding, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Substantive Change, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Documents, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Form A, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Form B, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
    - Home in School of Allied Health Professions, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Implementation Authorization Proposal, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Other Institutions, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Outlook, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 12-13)
    - Planning Committee, 1994-1998 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Planning Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Program Evaluation, American Physical Therapy Association, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Program Intention Statements, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Space, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Support Letters, 1992-1998 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - UW-System Collaborative, 2002-2005 (Box 30, Folder 20-21)
    - UW-System Collaborative, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Planning Document, 1982-1996 (Box 15, Folder 7-19)
  - President Obasanjo Visit, 2013
    Photographs from visit of Chief Olusegun Obasanjo, former president of Nigeria, to UWM campus in June 2013. Includes pictures of Chief Obasanjo and UWM officials touring Milwaukee and Lake Michigan.
  - Program Array Review, 1997-2002 (Box 31, Folder 2-5)
  - Program Descriptions, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Progressive Reform in the Care of the Mentally Ill, by Franklin Stein, 1960-1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)